{
    "id": "ef7abff12083443d85f1de1d42e9e596",
    "title": "Classification of nouns | exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c2fe625725014c96ae69d73f12c9558e",
            "title": "Classification Of Nouns",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The jury has announced its verdict. Jury is a .................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "abstract noun",
                        "collective noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sharon makes models from clay. Sharon is a ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "proper noun",
                        "collective noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Donald took out his pen and began to make notes. Pen is a .................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "proper noun",
                        "material noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The crocodiles in the river snapped angrily at the boat. River is a .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "proper noun",
                        "abstract noun",
                        "common noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boys on bicycles delivered pamphlets. Pamphlets is a ................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "proper noun",
                        "collective noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cleopatra was known for her beauty. Beauty is a / an .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "collective noun",
                        "abstract noun",
                        "common noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Always speak the truth. Truth is a ..............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "collective noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Nile overflows its banks every year. Nile is a ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "proper noun",
                        "collective noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I believe in his innocence. Innocence is a ....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "collective noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The elephant has great strength. Elephant is a .........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "collective noun",
                        "abstract noun",
                        "common noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}